crazylister.com 2017-01-21

# Crazylister Privacy Policy | World's Leading Design Software for eCommerce

### 1\. Introduction

1.1 This Privacy Policy is incorporated into CrazyLister’s User Agreement, and applies to the use of CrazyLister’s website, resources, services and products (hereafter referred to as “Resources”).

1.2. When you use CrazyLister’s Resources we track your activity and some of your personal information is used to identify you in our system, to interact with eBay on your behalf and to administer the site and to further improve our Resources to better suit you and your needs.

### 2\. What kind of information do we collect?

2.1. Information you provide.

a) You are required to create a CrazyLister’s account to gain access to our Resources. You also need to provide us with your eBay identifying token.b) We may supplement the information you provide to us with additional information gathered from other sources, such as publicly available information.

2.2. Data we collect.  

a) We collect all the information you provide when you use our Resources and also collect information about how you use our Resources, such as the types of content you view or engage with or the frequency and duration of your activities.  
b) we may also collect and store information such as your browser type, IP address, language, operating system, unique device identifier, the date and time of your visit, the pages you view and the websites you visited immediately before and after visiting CrazyLister’s website or used our Resources.

2.3. Our use of cookies (cookies policy).

a) Cookies are small files that are placed on your browser or device by the website or app you’re using. Pixel tags are small blocks of code on a webpage or app that allow them to do things like read and place cookies and transmit information to us or our partners. The resulting connection can include information such as a device’s IP address, the time a person viewed the pixel, an identifier associated with the browser or device and the type of browser being used. Local storage is an industry-standard technology that allows a website or app to store and retrieve data on a person’s computer, mobile phone or other device. Some examples include device or HTML5 local storage and caching.

b) We use “persistent cookies” to save your login information for future logins to CrazyLister’s Resources.

c) We use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of CrazyLister, to better understand how you interact with our Resources and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on our Resources.

d) Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but allow you to disable cookies through the “options” or “preferences” menu of your browser. Please be aware that disabling cookies could interfere with the functionality of CrazyLister’s Resources.

### 3\. How do we use your information at CrazyLister?

3.1. We use the information we collect to operate and provide you with our Resources and to administer the site and to further improve our Resources to better suit you. This includes, among other, the following use:

a) Authenticating your login;

b) Personalizing your user experience;

c) Customizing and delivering information about our products and services by email; Including marketing emails; You can opt out of receiving most emails by clicking “unsubscribe” at the bottom of the email, but we reserve the right to email you on certain circumstances such as when you request a reset password;

d) Providing customer service and sending confirmations about your account;  
e) Protecting our intellectual property or other rights; and

f) Managing and improving our business.

### 4\. No Disclosure to Third Parties for Their Own Marketing Purposes

We believe in protecting your privacy, and therefore do not provide your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes.

### 5\. When We Share Your Personal Information with Third Parties

5.1. We may share your personal information in the following ways:

a) Service providers and agents. We may share your information with certain third parties selected by us to help support our operations. These include, for example, services that help us process payments, analyze traffic, send emails, and track customer service requests. In addition, we may share limited personal information to third parties that help us market or advertise CrazyLister. These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf.

b) Affiliates. We may share your information with our corporate affiliates, such as entities under common ownership or control.

c) Business transfers. We may sell, transfer, or otherwise share some or all of our assets in connection with a merger, reorganization, business transaction, or in the event of bankruptcy. In such scenarios, your information may be one of the assets transferred. We will post a notice or otherwise notify you before the information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

d) Compliance with law and law enforcement requests, and protection of our rights. We may disclose your information when we have a good faith belief we are required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena, court order, or other legal mechanism. We may also disclose your information when we have a good faith belief that disclosure may prevent fraud and abuse of CrazyLister or its users or protect our property rights.

e) Consent. We may disclose your information when we believe we have your consent to do so, such as when you contact customer service and ask us about your account, or when we have the consent of someone we believe is authorized to consent on behalf of you. If you have expressly agreed to participate in a research study with us or with a third party that incorporates your personal information collected by CrazyLister, we also may disclose your information for the purpose of facilitating the research to which you have consented.

### 6\. Accessing, Reviewing, and Deleting Your Information

6.1. You can edit and change your information in your CrazyLister’s account, including your password, at any time and also delete all of the information we have collected about you by contacting us at the contact information listed below in section ‎10. While we will make reasonable efforts to accommodate your requests, if allowed by applicable laws, we reserve the right to impose certain requirements and restrictions on such requests, such as limiting our production of information to certain formats.

#### 7\. Security of Personal Information

We have implemented and maintain reasonable security practices to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of your personal information. However, no method of transmission or storage is completely secure, and we therefore cannot guarantee absolute security.

### 8\. Outside Israel Consent to Processing and Transfer of Information

If you access CrazyLister outside Israel, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the transfer of your personal information to, and the collection and processing of such personal information in Israel.

### 9\. Change Policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. If we make material changes, we will provide advance notice to you either by email, by posting a notification on an updated PP on CrazyLister’s website 15 days in advance of the effective date of the updated PP. Please note that, for existing users, unless otherwise provided by applicable law, your continued use of our Resources following the effective date, means that you agree with, and consent to be bound by, the updated PP.

### 10\. Contact Information

Please feel free to contact us at: vic@crazylister.com or via the contact form in our website.
